Why do you keep your disabled people in prisons?
你们为什么把监残障人士关在监狱
In prisons?
监狱
No. No.
不   不
We have some of the finest facilities in the world for the severely disabled.
我们是全球最好的重度残疾者机构
-I know, but they're run by prison guards. -No, not at all.
-我知道   但都是狱卒在管理   -不 并不是这样
Well, patient are kept out of sight.
但是病患都不见天日
Not treated as part of healthy society.
不被视为正常社会的一份子
I must ask that you withdraw that.
请你收回这句话
Mr. Cavendish doesn't mean to cause offense. He's meanly suggesting that the severely disabled
卡文迪什先生并不是故意冒犯你们   他只是建议重度残障者
can be better integrated into society.
能更好地融入社会
Absolutely. I can see that you all care very deeply about your disabled people.
没错   我看得出你们全部非常关心残障人士
I see that.
我看得出来
But let me ask you, when you look at me,
但请问你们   当你们看到我时
what is it that you see?
到底看到什么
Do you see a creature
只是看到一个
that's barely alive?
苟延残喘的生物
Or do you see a man that's escaped the confines
或者是一个从高强深锁的医院
of the hospital walls?
逃离禁锢的男人
Now I have a machine
现在我坐的轮椅下方
under this very seat that breathes for me.
有一台替我呼吸的机器
And at home, I have a ventilator right by my bed.
我家的床边也有 一台呼吸机